snowbird.com 2016-06-29

# Privacy Policy

**Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort Internet Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy governs Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort with regard to information it collects.

**About Our Privacy Policy**  
Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort respects your privacy. We will only collect, store and use the personal information we collect on our web sites for those purposes defined in this policy. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship and communication with you. Except as stated in this policy, we will not sell, rent or lease your personal information. At any time you may contact Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort with any questions or concerns that you have about this policy.

**When Personal Information Is Collected On Our Website**  
We may collect the personal information that you volunteer on registration, order, survey, sweepstakes entry, competition entry, or other forms, or by email.

We may collect personal information from your browser via Cookies, when you visit our web site and your browser interacts with our web site.

We may collect personal information when you make a purchase on our website.

**Use of Information Collected On Our Website**  
The information we collect on our website is used to develop better products, optimize your experience on our web sites and improve our communication with you so that we may maximize your Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort experience. We will always notify you, on the web page where you give us information and/or in the policy governing the contest, sweepstakes or special event or opportunity, if we intend to use your information differently than we have described in this privacy policy, as in the case of contests or sweepstakes. Please be sure to read these web pages or rules, as our use of the information collected there may vary from this Policy or from the policies that have governed previous contests, sweepstakes or other special event or opportunity.

We also use the information we collect online to support our off-line marketing activities, such as direct mail.

**Information We Share With Others**  
Except as stated in this policy, we will not sell, lease or rent your personal information to any third party.

We never give your email address or telephone number to third parties, including our partner companies.

We sometimes employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. For example, hosting our website and database, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links, analyzing data, etc. These third parties have access to personal information needed to perform these functions, but may not use it for other purposes and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

**Use of Information Collected After Sale or Merger**  
In the event that Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort is sold, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information could be one of the transferred assets.

**Disclosure**  
In certain special cases, we may disclose your personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort’s rights, property or operations, other Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort site users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, a pending civil case, administrative investigation or investigation conducted by Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort. We shall have no obligation to inform you of our compliance with the law, including without limitation a response to a law enforcement request or a valid subpoena.

**Links**  
Our website may enable you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others through our online forum, The Bird’s Nest. When you use this service, the information that you share may be collected by other visitors. We do not provide any type of security or protection for information that you provide in The Bird’s Nest. Information concerning the policies and procedures that govern The Bird’s Nest is available on the web site. We reserve the right to censor information that we deem to be distasteful, harmful or otherwise inappropriate on The Bird’s Nest.

Our website also contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other web sites. We encourage you to note when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies listed on these (and all) third party sites. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort’s web site. If you choose to provide information on a thirdparty site, that information will be subject to that party's privacy policy.

**Cookies**  
We may use cookies from time-to-time to help you, for example, to navigate efficiently between secure and non-secure pages of our site; to participate in sweepstakes or monthly drawings; or to help us identify special interests that you may have and that enhance your experience on our websites. "Cookies" are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use all of the features of our site, including purchasing tickets and other products online. We may track the web site you come from or go to. We may track what browser you use so as to send you pages appropriate for your browser. We may also collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. We may use this information for the operation of online services, to maintain quality of online services, and to provide general statistics regarding use of this website.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

**Security**  
Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort operates secure data networks protected by firewall and password protection. Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every reasonable effort to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

You must promptly notify us if your credit card, user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number from our system and/or cancel a pass product, user name or password and update our records accordingly.

**Review or Change your Information or Preferences** You may ask us whether we are keeping personal information about you by sending an email, with your complete name and address to: info@snowbird.com or by sending postal mail to this address: Attn: Database Marketing Manager, Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort, P.O. Box 929000, Snowbird, Utah, 84092- 9000. We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal information that we keep about you within thirty days of your request, without charge. You may correct, amend or delete any of your information or change your preferences.

**Visitor Choice Opt-in/Opt-out Program**  
Opt in: You may choose to receive promotional or marketing information from this website by going to http://www.snowbird.com/about/enews.html and filling out the opt-in form.

**Opt-out:**  
If you are receiving promotional or marketing information from this web site and no longer wish to receive such information, you may choose to opt-out or unsubscribe by going to http://www.snowbird.com/about/enews.html or by sending an email to info@snowbird.com. Each time we contact you via email using your personal information, we will offer you an opportunity to opt-out or unsubscribe, either entirely or for specific purposes. Please note that our online subscription database is for email marketing programs only. To opt-out from all communications including direct mail, please change your preferences by sending an email to info@snowbird.com or by sending postal mail to: Attn: Database Marketing Manager, Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort, P.O. Box 929000, Snowbird, Utah, 84092-9000.

**Children's Privacy (Age 12 and Under)**  
We are concerned about the safety of children and will comply, at all times, with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect email subscription information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have email subscription information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems as soon as we discover that it has been submitted it and we will not disclose it to third parties.

**Privacy Support**  
If you would like more information regarding our use of your personal information, or you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
Attn: Database Marketing Manager  
Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort  
P.O. Box 929000  
Snowbird, Utah, 84092-9000

Or by email: info@snowbird.com

**VERY IMPORTANT:**  
If you feel that we have not posted an acceptable privacy policy, or are not following the privacy policy posted, please send us an email at info@snowbird.com. If appropriate, we may forward complaints to the appropriate third parties and help you follow up to ensure that your concerns are adequately handled. Of course, if any of these third party companies does not have a privacy policy that is acceptable to you, you should refrain from providing information until your concerns have been satisfactorily addressed.

Snowbird Ski and Summer Resort reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be posted to this page, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you of any significant changes to this privacy policy. However, it is your responsibility to check this site for any such updates as you will be bound by them should you choose to visit our site.
